A Guide to the Records of T. Marshall Hahn Jr, 1962-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series VII, 1973-1974
  - Geological Science Department, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3076)
  - Glee Club, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3077)
  - Governor of Va. #1, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3078)
  - Governor of Va. #2, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3079)
  - Governor of Va. (Earl J. Shiflet Secretary of Commerce and Resources), 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3080)
  - Governor's Day, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3081)
  - Graduate School, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3082)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3083)
  - Dr Hahn - Personal #1, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3084)
  - Dr Hahn - Personal #2, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3085)
  - Dr Hahn - Personal #3, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 3086)
  - Dr Hahn - Personal #4, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3087)
  - Dr Hahn - Biographical Sketches and Photographs, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3088)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3089)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3090)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3091)
  - Health Education and Welfare, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3092)
  - Highway Department, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3093)
  - History Department, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3094)
  - Homecoming, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3095)
  - Home Economics, College of, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3096)
  - Horticulture Department, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3097)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3098)
  - Industrial Engineering Department, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3099)
  - Information Services #1, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3100)
  - Information Services #2, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3101)
  - Information Services #3, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3102)
  - Institutional Research #1, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3103)
  - Institutional Research #2, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3104)
  - Invitations - Inaugurations, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3105)
  - Invitations - Miscellaneous #1, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3106)
  - Invitations - Miscellaneous #2, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3107)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3108)
  - Johnston, J. Ambler, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3109)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3110)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3111)
  - The Lane Company, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3112)
  - Learning Resources Center, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3113)
  - Legislators - U. S. Congress #1, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3114)
  - Legislators - U. S. Congress #2, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3115)
  - Legislators - General Assembly #1, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3116)
  - Legislators - General Assembly #2, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3117)
  - Legislators - General Assembly #3, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3118)
  - Library, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3119)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3120)
- Series VIII, 1948-1974, n.d.
  - Miscellaneous #1, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3121)
  - Miscellaneous #2, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3122)
  - Miscellaneous #3, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3123)
  - Mathematics Department, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3124)
  - Mechanical Engineering Department, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3125)
  - Minerals - Engineering, Division of, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3126)
  - Mineral Research Lab, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3127)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3128)
  - Naming Buildings, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3129)
  - National Science Foundation #1, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3130)
  - National Science Foundation #2, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3131)
  - NASA, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3132)
  - Norfolk Area Medical Center, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3133)
  - Oakridge Associated Universities (ORAU), 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3134)
  - Occupational Safety and Health - T. Carl Shelton Jr., 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3135)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3136)
  - Paller and Container Research Center, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3137)
  - Performing Arts and Communications, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3138)
  - Personnel - A. T. Butt, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3139)
  - Personnal - Richmond, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3140)
  - Philippines, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3141)
  - Physics Department, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3142)
  - Placement, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3143)
  - Plant Pathology Department, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3144)
  - Political Science Department, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3145)
  - Psychology Department, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3146)
  - Purchasing, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3147)
  - Presidential Search, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3148)
  - Receptions, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3149)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3150)
  - Recommendations #1, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3151)
  - Recommendations #2, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3152)
  - Registrar, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3153)
  - Research Division #1, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3154)
  - Research Division #2, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3155)
  - Retirement, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3156)
  - Reynolds Homestead Research Center, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3157)
  - ROTC, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3158)
  - Ross, David L., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3159)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3160)
  - Salvation Army, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3161)
  - Savage, Lon K., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3162)
  - Scholarships and Grants #1, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3163)
  - Scholarships and Grants #2, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3164)
  - Scholarships and Grants #3, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3165)
  - Security Department, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3166)
  - Sociology Department, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3167)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3168)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) #1, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3169)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) #2, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3170)
  - Speaking Engagement, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3171)
  - Speeches, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3172)
  - Speech Material, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3173)
  - Sporn Awards, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3174)
  - Staff Meetings #1, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3175)
  - Staff Meetings #2, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3176)
  - State Council on Higher Education #1, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3177)
  - State Council on Higher Education #2, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3178)
  - State Council on Higher Education #3, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3179)
  - State Council on Higher Education #4, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3180)
  - State Council on Higher Education #5, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3181)
  - State Council on Higher Education #6, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3182)
  - Statistics Department, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3183)
  - Student Affairs - Payne, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3184)
  - Student Government Association #1, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3185)
  - Student Housing #1, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3186)
  - Student Housing #2, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3187)
  - Student Housing #3, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3188)
  - Student Housing #4, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3189)
  - Virginia Academy of Sciences, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3190)
  - Student Letters - To and From, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3191)
  - Student Letters - Others #1, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3192)
  - Student Letters - Others #2, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3193)
  - Student Residence Program - Hill, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3194)
  - Student Organizations, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3195)
  - Student Services, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3196)
  - Student Union, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3197)
  - Subscriptions, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3198)
  - Summer School Programs, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3199)
  - Task Force For Innovative Approaches to Instruction #1, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3200)
  - Telecommunications, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3201)
  - Tenure, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 3202)
  - University Council #1, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3203)
  - University Council #2, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3204)
  - University Council #3, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3205)
  - University Professors, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3206)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprises, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3207)
  - Upward Bound, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3208)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3209)
  - Veterinary Science Department, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3210)
  - Proposed College of Veterinary Medicine in Virginia #1, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3211)
  - Proposed College of Veterinary Medicine in Virginia #2, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3212)
  - Proposed College of Veterinary Medicine in Virginia #3, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3213)
  - Proposed College of Veterinary Medicine in Virginia #4, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3214)
  - Proposed College of Veterinary Medicine in Virginia #5, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3215)
  - Vice President - Academic Affairs #1, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3216)
  - Vice President - Academic Affairs #2, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3217)
  - Vice President - Administration, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3218)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #1, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3219)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #2, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3220)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #3, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3221)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #4, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3222)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs #5, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3223)
  - Executive Vice President #1, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3224)
  - Executive Vice President #2, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3225)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Commerce #1, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3226)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Commerce #2, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3227)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3228)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association #1, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3229)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association #2, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3230)
  - Virginia Tech Student Aid Association, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3231)
  - Virginia Truck Experimental Station, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3232)
  - Virginia Tidewater Consortium For Continuing Higher Education, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3233)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3234)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3235)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, Pres. Fund, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3236)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3237)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3238)
  - Western Region Consortium For Continuing Education #1, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3239)
  - Western Region Consortium For Continuing Education #2, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3240)
  - 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3241)
  - Y - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 3242)
  - Pratt, John Lee, 1948-1951 (Box 96, Folder 3243)
  - Pratt, John Lee, 1953-1962 (Box 96, Folder 3244)
  - Pratt, John Lee, 1963-1968 (Box 96, Folder 3245)
  - Pratt, John Lee, 1969-1973 (Box 96, Folder 3246)
  - Local, Regional and State Government Modernization, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3247)
  - Office of the President - T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., 1962-74 (Box 97, Folder 3248)
  - Capital Outlay, 1966-74 (Box 97, Folder 3249)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, Pamphlets, etc... Pulled from files, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3250)
  - Inauguration #1 (Thomas Marshall Hahn, Jr.), April 4, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 3251)
  - Inauguration #2, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3252)
  - Inauguration #3, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3253)
  - Inauguration #4, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3254)
  - Speeches, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 3255)
  - Speeches, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 3256)
  - Speeches, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 3257)
  - Speeches, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 3258)
  - Speeches, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 3259)
  - Speeches, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 3260)
  - Speeches, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 3261)
  - Speeches, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 3262)
  - Speeches, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 3263)
  - Speeches, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 3264)
  - Speeches, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 3265)
  - Speeches, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 3266)
  - VARC, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 3267)
  - VARC, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 3268)
  - VARC #1, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 3269)
  - VARC #2, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 3270)
  - VARC #1, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 3271)
  - VARC #2, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 3272)
  - VARC #3, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 3273)
  - VARC - Research Council Minutes, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3273a)
  - VARC - Report on Audit, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3273b)
  - VARC - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3273c)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 3274)
  - Change in Corp of Cadets, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 3275)
  - Press History of the Change in the Corps of Cadets, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 3276)
  - Letters Regarding the Status of the Corps of Cadets at VPI, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 3277)
  - News for Farmer Cooperatives, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3277a)
  - Scrapbook of Articles and Clippings, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3277b)
  - MASC #1, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3278)
  - MASC #2, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3279)
  - MASC #3, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3280)
  - MASC #4, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3281)
  - MASC #5, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3282)
  - MASC #6, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3283)
  - MASC, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3284)
  - MASC - Consultants, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3285)
  - MASC - Executive Committee, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3286)
  - MASC - Federal Agencies Contacts, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3287)
  - MASC - Finance or Funding, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3288)
  - MASC - Inquiries to other states, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3289)
  - MASC - Members' Correspondence, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3290)
  - MASC - Minutes, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3291)
  - MASC - Other State Studies, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3292)
  - MASC - Requests for Report, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3293)
  - MASC - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3294)
  - MASC #1, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 3295)
  - MASC #2, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 3296)
  - MASC #3, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 3297)
  - MASC #4, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3298)
  - MASC - Commission's Work Program, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3299)
  - MASC - Consultants, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3300)
  - MASC - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3301)
  - MASC - Funding, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3302)
  - MASC - Gov't Structure Com., 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3303)
  - MASC - Hearings, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3304)
  - MASC - Mr. Edwin Holm, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3305)
  - MASC - (Persons Requesting Copy of Interim Report), 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3306)
  - MASC - Director: Mr. Richard H. Kraft, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3307)
  - MASC - Legal Counsel, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3308)
  - MASC - Legislation, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3309)
  - MASC - Members, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3310)
  - MASC - Minutes, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3311)
  - MASC - Other States, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3312)
  - MASC - Press Releases, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3313)
  - MASC - Problems, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3314)
  - MASC - Proposed Legislation, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3315)
  - MASC - Resolutions, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3316)
  - MASC - Welfare, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3317)
  - MASC - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3318)
  - Press Clippings from Conference on Artificial Satellites, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3277c)
  - Handwritten speech: "Role of the Academic Community in Campus Unrest", n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3319)